[somber music playing]
[grunting]
We're locked inside again.
[sighs] What the hell do we do now?
Something must've gone wrong. Relax, okay?
What about Keila? Huh?
She was outside, but the doors closed.
That guy must've done something to her.
Shit!
Keila has a camera.
Whatever happened,
Damián and Berlin saw it.
So stop imagining things.
What things, Roi?
That guy's a psychopath who put you
in a cage and threw you into the river.
Oh, I don't know. He shot me in the foot,
and Keila ran him over with the pickup.
And to top it all,
he knows she's a professional thief,
and she just happens to be standing
in front of the door
where he hides his cash.
Still think I'm imagining it?
This is really fucking bad, Roi.
The duke told him to lay off.
She's gonna be fine.
[sighs]
And now this. Fucking lights. [sighs]
Door closes, the lights go off.
The door opens… the lights go on.
- Funny, Roi.
- Yeah?
- [metallic clang]
- [ominous music rises]
Hey, kiddos. Let's get to work.
And Keila? Where is she?
With Berlin. She's okay, though.
What are we supposed to do?
What if someone comes back?
That's exactly what I said to Berlin.
And what if someone comes back?
Risk is a big part of the beauty
of our profession,
but this time it might be in our favor.
The warden's already been
down to the chapel,
and hasn't noticed
anything out of the ordinary.
Now he's in the kitchen, having coffee.
[Berlin] He doesn't seem very worried.
I hope nobody needs to make
a cash withdrawal in the next 20 minutes.
Let's hope for the best.
Because otherwise, the only way out
will be to shoot your way out.
[energetic music playing]
I can't believe I'm about to be locked up
in here for a third time.
Crypt is sealed now.
[intriguing music playing]
I put a hidden camera inside the chapel.
- We've got eyes on us.
- Mm.
Now, let's see
what he has behind this door.
You brought the GPR?
Mm-hmm. And I also brought the biosonar.
We have to map out what's inside.
Whatever's in there, we're gonna find it.
We've got a problem.
The duke's coming this way.
Do you mind?
- [Berlin chuckles nonchalantly]
- I don't want to bother you.
Forgive me if… I steal
a few minutes of your time.
[chuckles]
[tense music fades]
She's a mystery to me. Truly fascinating.
Enigmatic, I would say.
I see that you are focused on finding
a solution for our business endeavor.
But where is the rest of the team?
[scanner beeping]
They're doing what they do best.
Each of them has
a specialized network of contacts
that enable us to gather
all the necessary tools for our heist.
Thermal lances, biosensors,
vehicles, all the rest.
Sewage systems, security systems,
you know, all that kinda stuff.
"All that kinda stuff."
So… do you know
how you're going to steal it?
I really am looking forward
to telling you all about it,
but I'm still working on a few details.
Hmm.
You cannot believe how exciting it is
to be the promoter
of the heist of the century.
Elaborating a plan of this magnitude is
the same as forging a work of art,
a masterpiece.
Mm. I am so excited to learn
about the details of your idea.
We’re waiting for that little spark
of genius that changes everything.
[mimics explosion, chuckles]
- [sighs]
- [mimics explosion]
[all laugh]
Well then, I'll be off.
I won't bother you anymore,
except to invite you all over for dinner.
9:30. And…
the dress code is black tie.
Of course, if you need Samuel to bring you
to see a tailor or… to a boutique…
[Berlin] That won't be necessary.
I always pack my bags to be ready
for all occasions.
Black tie, white tie, pink tie…
Pink tie? [laughs]
[laughs]
I like a sense of humor.
All right, see you later.
[Berlin] Mm.
[sighs]
We're about to have problems
with this stupid ignoramus.
What kind of problems?
Didn't you notice
how he checked all of our laptops?
Spying on us,
poking his nose around like a sniffer dog,
wanting to explore
every single millimeter.
To me, he seemed involved
and excited about the job.
Like an exuberant boss.
No, no, no. You’re mistaken.
[plays menacing piano notes]
Sure, the man looks
like a complete buffoon,
acts like a monkey.
But don't be fooled.
He's a criminal mastermind.
It will compel us to be extra careful.
The fact that he came
to snoop around means
that he's anxious and doesn't trust us.
So, what do we do now?
[tense music rises]
We devise a magnificent scheme
to rob the painting,
a perfect plan, a real plan.
As if we really intended to steal it.
I will handle this one personally.
So, we're gonna work on a perfect plan
and steal nothing?
That's exactly it.
I'll make a plan to indulge that idiot.
A true masterpiece of grand larceny.
Keila, take a few notes.
Start hacking
like your life depends on it.
Find out when
and where the portrait leaves Poland,
the flight number to Spain, and the name
of the company in charge of transport.
[chuckles]
[flamenco-inspired theme music playing]
What is it?
There has to be some kind of mechanism
that opens the door from inside.
If someone comes to steal, doors close.
They're not gonna have
a "press here" sign.
The scans been completed. Let's go.
And how do we get out of this place?
With Swiss precision.
Keila, eyes on us.
There are a few servants
moving up the stairs.
Head to the east wing.
Did you bring a tux?
[duke] Good evening, everyone.
All afternoon, I've been thinking
about how I can make
this evening's get-together
unforgettable… exceptional.
And, badam… suddenly,
sitting in the mauve room,
I felt inspired
by the light of the chandeliers,
and I thought to myself,
"Why not a good old-fashioned dinner?"
Like back in the 18th century,
by candlelight, when all this was founded.
And so, friends, let me raise my glass
and toast to your success.
And to mine.
[light guitar music playing]
[Keila] What a magical ambiance.
Indeed. The candlelight is divine.
[Damián] I love the scent.
- Thanks a lot.
- [Roi] Thank you.
- [Roi] Is this apricot?
- [Genoveva] It's bergamot. From India.
- [Roi] That's quite exotic.
- [Genoveva] Mm-hmm.
[tense music rises]
I know this might not be the right time,
but I have something important to say.
These past few days,
I've been a little distracted.
It's 'cause I found out
Keila's having an affair.
At first… it seemed to be
an unimportant sexual encounter,
but things have escalated, and…
and now it has become a romance.
Bruce, please. Please stop.
No, Keila, no.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
And I don't mean this in any weird way,
or that you should feel sorry for me.
When I learned about the affair, I mean…
it devastated me.
[sighs]
But then, she said that she loved me…
That I'm wonderful,
that I'm from another planet and that…
[sighs] …she won't leave me.
[music grows tender]
And I won't leave her either.
And so…
Keila…
[tense music peaks, fades]
…I say we have a three-way.
[whimsical music playing]
A three-way?
Like a throuple, Roi.
Keila…
the dude and me.
Shit. You're a serious moron, aren't you?
You know what Roi?
I'm more of a creator than a destroyer.
You wouldn't understand.
[sighs] What do you think, Keila?
[Keila] I'm feeling overwhelmed,
my heart's beating so fast
it's tachycardic,
and my… brain's about to explode,
and, you know,
maybe… we should ask the third person
what he thinks.
We will ask him.
Over coffee, or… whatever,
but I need you to answer me now.
Well…
I suppose that
it's something maybe worth exploring.
I guess.
Just perfect.
A toast, then? Yeah?
- To the throuple.
That's quite a start
to our dinner. [laughs]
I see that your gang is very, very modern.
- [under breath] Yeah.
- Don't you agree, darling?
Absolutely. In fact, I would say they're…
a breath of fresh air.
We, on the other hand,
are more traditional, I'd say.
Darling, can you imagine us
in a three-way?
[Genoveva laughs] I don't know.
[duke] C'mon, let yourself go.
Let yourself be inspired by this…
aura of liberty that has entered our home.
Try to imagine… you… and me…
and a pretty, let's say…
Mm…
Scandinavian woman.
- An international trio.
- [laughs]
[Genoveva] I see. [chuckles]
Well… my preference would be for two men.
- [coughs]
- [Genoveva] With you, obviously, my love.
And with… let's say… a Brazilian…
- Mm. [laughs]
- …for example.
Damián, what do you think about all this?
[Damián] Hm. Uh…
I think that in life we make a choice
to be a bonobo or a swan.
And what is any of that supposed to mean?
Well, the swan is one of
the few species that's monogamous.
And romantic.
The bonobo ape is libertine
and promiscuous.
The more the merrier.
[gentle music playing]
In my case, I'm more a swan.
You're a swan?
[whimsical music playing]
So… you're… monogamous?
Hopelessly so. Mm-hmm.
Although I can imagine
it's a lot of fun being a bonobo.
I wouldn't judge anyone.
It's just that, for me,
love is about focusing on one person…
And that focus makes you happy.
[duke] Fascinating.
And what does the head
of the gang think about all of this?
Do you think that one can be fulfilled
by the love of a single person,
and that that one person
can infuse us with happiness?
May I offer you some wine?
So what happens if we fall
in love with someone else?
Does that imply that we shall be twice
as happy?
Any thoughts about this?
[Berlin chuckles]
I'd have to say I don't agree.
I prefer the theory
of communicating vessels.
Let me explain.
Two glasses equally full don't exist.
If one of them is full,
it's because… the other is empty.
Ooh, wow.
[smacks lips] I'll need a refill.
But let me continue.
It is my opinion
that love does not require
two or more half-full glasses.
The only thing that love requires
is one glass… filled to the brim.
[grunts, chuckles]
Do you know this wine?
Hmm?
"Tomorrow. 8:00 p.m.
Dinner on your boat for 500,000."
I really like your white shirt.
God save us all! Unreal.
Can somebody tell me what
that dinner was supposed to be about?
Because I couldn't distinguish
the stew from the truffles.
It's the same kind of show
that you would have done.
A twilight world of decadent beauty,
sex, wine, and candlesticks, dripping wax…
A dreamscape from Lord Byron.
Right?
Firstly, I'm not a fan of Byron.
And secondly, I want
as little contact possible with this guy.
'Cause I want to destroy him.
Back to work, all of you!
Can we? For a moment?
You won't believe what happened.
The duchess is on fire.
Here we are,
making photocopies like real amateurs.
Meanwhile, she has redesigned the label
on the bottle of wine.
I don't understand.
She wrote a message on the label,
of a bottle of wine…
in small print, seamlessly disguised
as part of the vintage design.
- The same typography of the '96 Rioja.
- Oh!
- Isn't she devilish?
- Mm-hm.
She's good.
She sent you a message,
hidden in the design of a wine label.
[both laugh]
It's a bit risqué, don't you think?
Mm. Madness can be a blessing.
The adrenaline and the passion
and the perils.
You see, the thing is,
she asked me for a signal.
I had to wear a white shirt.
And then, we had dinner plans
and the dress code.
You can't just break protocol.
But I think she took that
as a sign that I said yes.
She's out to get me.
Yeah, and now it seems
you've got the jitters.
Maybe, but I also have my responsibilities
as a member of the gang and as a man.
So I have decided that
the best course of action is not to go.
You're a foolish and stubborn swan.
My friend, I'm sorry to be the one
to break it to you,
however, not seeing her
won't solve anything.
Don't you see it? She'll never stop!
- If you don't submit… our plan will fail.
- So what is it that you want me to do?
Go on that date,
and you become her best friend.
Invite her for ice cream,
tell her about your mom,
the best way to put an end to passion.
And above all, just
remember, if you don't screw…
we can't get screwed.
The rest of you analyze all the data
we scanned from the crypt.
I want to know once and for all
what is behind that door.
[intense music playing]
[doorbell rings]
[rabbit squeaks]
May we come in?
Who is this beautiful beast you have here?
- Her name is Mandarin.
- Ooh.
I was thinking that she might
be good company for Pomelo.
I got the feeling
he was a little possessive.
Maybe jealous of me.
Now the four of us can be together.
In that case, come on in.
Let me introduce you guys
and see how you get along.
Look, Pomelo,
I brought you a little friend.
Don't worry, baby. Look how cute she is.
Don't worry… Her name is Mandarin.
I apologize,
I'm really sorry about waking you up
like that in the middle of the night.
[sighs]
You have no idea how happy it made me
to hear that doorbell ring
in the middle of the night.
To find you.
Well… both of you.
Do you know why?
Because earlier this morning,
when you sent me that message
about your dinner with the duke.
Well… to be honest…
I did feel a little bit neglected.
I know that sounds silly.
There was no reason for me to be there.
It's professional,
and you have a job to do at the palace…
But my feelings were hurt.
[sighs]
Ridiculous, huh?
And the reason that I felt that way…
is because… I'm starting
to fall in love with you.
That's why I wanted to ask you…
how you feel.
[cell phone vibrating]
- Sorry.
- No rest for the wicked.
24-hour service.
Go ahead.
One moment.
[sighs]
[exhales]
Cameron?
- We've arrived in Saïdia.
- It has a nice beach.
I imagine that all of those wealthy,
distinguished guests have booked
an excursion to the desert?
Exactly. Luckily for me,
the boats' crew were also sent to shore.
It appears the yacht
had electrical issues.
They told us it would take
eight hours to repair.
Only two sailors and the captain
have remained on board.
To avoid raising any suspicions,
I said I wanted to visit Cabo de Agua.
Will I have enough time?
Yeah. But why would you wanna go there?
My grandad's from Chafarinas.
I read on the Internet that you can see
the islands from the lighthouse.
I suppose then it's your lucky day.
[Cameron] I pretended to be really excited
about the trip and ran off.
But I stayed on the docks to keep watch.
Are you sure no one saw you?
Absolutely.
[mysterious music playing]
I went back and forth, buying groceries
all day, potatoes, bread, fruit…
I'd go to the far end of the market,
throw it away and start again.
And during that whole time,
no one came to repair the boat.
But there was a delivery.
A pallet of Nigerian rice.
That's the most unusual thing, though,
'cause I've been down to the galley,
and it's full of rice.
Rice from Valencia.
And where's the rice from Nigeria?
Don't know. I'm gonna look for it
once we're out in the open.
You keep me informed.
[rabbits squeak]
[sighs]
[exhales]
So, you want to know how I feel? Well…
I feel like any man…
would feel when he spends
the evening with strangers.
I think about you.
I think about you every time
the conversation turns to love.
I am supposed to be thinking
about how to beat the security
to the palace vault.
And again, late tonight,
I was still thinking about you.
And then I had this crazy idea of finding
a pet store called Miracle,
and thankfully it was… still open,
which meant I was able to find
this cutie… the prettiest bunny
in the whole wide world.
This wasn't easy. I spent hours
and hours on specialized sites,
just to figure out the difference
between females and males,
and I finally succeeded.
After that, at 2:55 in the morning,
I jumped into a taxi
and drove halfway across the city
and suddenly found myself at your door.
I raced up the stairs,
my heart beating faster and faster,
and finally… I rang your doorbell.
I couldn't wait…
[sighs]
…to see you again.
[chuckles] And so,
to answer your question,
what is it you would think that
a man feels when he does all that?
Well, I would say… that man is bewitched.
[sighs]
And he's…
somewhat in love.
You cannot imagine how much.
[rabbit squeaks]
[chuckles]
I'm not sure this'll work.
He's asleep
[both laugh]
Are you tired?
Me? Sleep is the furthest thing
from my mind.
I am delighted because we are going
to prepare a plan together.
What do we plan to rob?
The Lady with the Ermine.
You are gonna love this. [chuckles]
[both laugh]
I'm very familiar
with this type of system.
The security code contains
up to 16 alphanumeric characters.
I'm pretty sure I can break
the code in under seven minutes.
Considering how complex it was
in the gallery,
this is surprisingly simple.
Doesn't make sense.
Well, maybe he values his art
above his money.
[sighs]
Down there, he has millions of euros
in dirty money.
I find it hard to believe that someone
like the duke hasn't built something
that's impenetrable.
Or maybe the door
doesn't need that much security.
Keila, the outline's been rendered.
All the data from the georadar
and biosensor has been downloaded.
Oh, yeah!
[funky music playing]
Rhythm is something
you're born with or not.
"Elvis the Pelvis."
- C'mon, Keila, focus.
- Sorry.
Now, let's see exactly
what's behind those walls of his.
[Keila] The door leads
to a circular corridor.
It kind of looks like the antechamber
to a secret vault.
It's like an igloo.
[Keila] Judging by the data we collected,
it appears to be made of titanium plates.
To me, it seems pretty impenetrable.
- That's strange.
- What do you mean?
Why not leave the vault out in the open?
Why surround it with that corridor?
Maybe he thinks titanium
clashes with the decor.
It's not easy to find a match
with a snakeskin carpet.
- [laughs]
- [chuckles]
Don't you think it looks like a bullring?
We know he loves bullfighting.
Maybe it's an added security ring.
And the inner vault door…
it doesn't have a lever or a handle.
Not even hydraulics.
There's nothing to open it.
And there's something strange
right here. Look.
The walls have two layers.
They're doubled up. There!
Why would anyone bother making
a hollow cavity between steel walls?
- It makes the structure vulnerable.
- Let me see.
What was that?
I'm using colors to identify
different densities.
Oxygen is blue.
Red is something else.
Not sure what. Probably gas.
- Gas?
- [Keila] Yeah.
I don't get it.
It might be some kind of narcotic?
Well, knowing the duke,
narcotics would make sense,
but in my opinion,
it's gas, and probably inflammable.
I'd say it's pumped in
through these nozzles.
Zoom in.
[Roi] What kind of gas?
Hydrogen, methane, acetylene… not sure.
So are you saying that the duke
built that corridor to make a barbecue?
Exactly.
It's a trap like in Indiana Jones.
He seems to like that.
Remember the hand of the angel
that opened the crypt?
What do you mean, Damián?
That whoever goes inside is cooked?
Like a hot dog?
That's insane.
Whoever gets in there,
Roi, has already made it
into the Duke's palace,
then made it to the chapel.
Found their way into the crypt,
then made their way
across the snakeskin carpet
and still managed to crack
the security code to the vault.
In his world, the punishment is death.
We have no reason to believe that.
The logical assumption
is that the gas activates something.
First, the hatch will be closed,
then it releases the gas,
and then we burst into flames,
and then we die.
[Keila] You're talking
like he's a psychopath.
Or some kind of crazy serial killer.
We have absolutely no evidence
to prove it. Let me analyze this first.
I need time to think about this.
[sighs]
[gentle music rises]
[door opens]
[gasps]
What are you doing here?
I… wasn't able to sleep, and so
I came here to get some fresh air
to forget my worries.
[tense music playing]
Love?
Or heartbreak?
Professional problems?
Tell me what kind of worries
keep you awake.
Well, I have to say
it's mostly professional.
This job poses significant challenges.
And I can't seem
to stop my mind from spinning.
[duke chuckles]
I know exactly what you mean.
That… spiraling obsession.
Luckily I have a remedy.
Oh! It's infallible.
Come this way.
[exhales]
[tense music fades]
[sighs]
[energetic music playing]
My brain's about to explode.
I need some rest.
I'll be with you in a second.
Tell me, when did you lose your dignity?
This is so sad.
No, in fact, it's embarrassing.
Aren't you ashamed,
all that brown-nosing and bending over?
And what was all that throuple stuff?
In front of the duke
and duchess and everyone? Huh?
Making her an offer she couldn't refuse.
Man, that was fucking pathetic.
What was pathetic Roi?
Expressing my true feelings, is that it?
No. Bruce, listen, the problem is
that you asked the girl that you love
to fuck some other guy.
Wake up, man.
It's not like I'm fucking trying
to strategize. Hmm?
It's a philosophy for life.
A philosophy? Of what?
Well, it's about love, Roi. Just love.
I'm not sure you know about it,
but love inspires
much more than hate does.
It's what defines us as humans.
- Right.
- You know what else?
I am absolutely sure
that I'm gonna suffer because of this.
But that's okay.
Who do you think you are? Gandhi?
Because just a few minutes ago,
you were dressed like Elvis.
You were making a fool of yourself
in front of your girl.
Didn't you see her laugh? [chuckles]
I've got some bad news for you.
The guy you're up against…
is a photographer,
an adventurer, a graphic designer…
And apparently,
he's a fucking fountain of sensitivity.
Bruce, I'm afraid Elvis
has left the building.
[chuckles]
I've got news for you too.
I was Keila's first love ever,
and she was 36.
Do you know why, Roi?
I asked about her panties
and about her pussy
and all the stupid stuff.
The fact is, she fell for me.
Not the smart one. Mm?
To be honest, Roi, art… is very overrated.
[scoffs]
- [under breath] Fuck me. Great.
- [door closes]
[horse neighs]
Here we are.
This is my secret haven
where I stop the compulsive ruminating.
And the anxiety.
[chuckles]
Easy, boy, easy.
[horse snorts]
Come. Look. This is Prince.
I call it equine therapy. [chuckles]
Go ahead. Touch him.
That's it.
Touch his mane.
Talk to him. So he knows your voice.
- How are you, my Prince?
- Easy boy.
- What's wrong?
- Give him a hug.
Go ahead.
How?
- Hug him. He won't hurt you.
- Like this?
[chuckles] Not like that. Let me show you.
Wrap your arms around his neck.
Easy, boy. Easy, boy.
[exhales] You have to feel his warmth.
And when you hear
the horse's heart beating,
focus on your own heartbeat.
Then you'll notice how they beat in sync.
[gentle music playing]
Don't be shy.
[Prince neighs softly]
Concentrate on your breathing.
And synchronize with the horse's breath.
You'll reach a point…
where you'll both be breathing
13 times per minute.
Let him guide you.
Let him set the tempo, the pauses…
The depth of your breathing.
Soon, your body
will begin to release oxytocin.
And you'll feel at peace.
A feeling that is extraordinary.
[Prince breathing loudly]
I can feel that sense of peace.
[chuckles]
Please enjoy it.
Because that feeling
is on its way to extinction,
like all good things.
Right, Prince?
Same for me. I'll soon be extinct too.
How's that?
Well… there's hastiness… and telephones
and throuples.
And with all of this, the world
we belong to will come to an end.
I'm a swan too. I get it.
You could say that…
we are monogamous horse whispering men.
I don't know what to think.
Nor do I. [chuckles]
This conversation…
requires some fine wine.
Tell me, what is it you want?
Nothing, really. I just wanted to clear
a few things up about this guy, Claudio.
For me, Claudio,
he's… kind of like a visitor.
A guest. Right?
This is new for both of us,
and I'm doing my best, but…
I think you're gonna need
to meet me halfway.
Halfway to where Bruce? I'm lost.
You're very generous,
and I'm trying to navigate this.
Now I feel even more lost than before.
[Bruce sighs]
[somber music playing]
[sighs, panting]
Bruce, what if it's a bad idea?
In life, we have to make choices,
and I think my choice is selfish.
It's okay, Keila.
I just wanna make sure
that we agree on a few boundaries.
Like what?
Well…
I'd prefer it if you didn't share
your umbrella with him when it rains.
And you cannot share gelato…
or popcorn when watching movies.
Each has their own bucket.
And definitely no singing together
at karaoke.
And I'd rather…
you not share
your virtual reality world with him.
Please.
You told me I was
the only one who'd ever seen it.
Yeah?
Tell me you haven't shown him.
["Caballo Prieto Azabache"
by Antonio Aguilar playing]
[in Spanish] ♪ With three Mauser shots ♪
♪ You ran, jet black, saving my life ♪
♪ What you did for me ♪
♪ Horse friend, I won't forget ♪
♪ I couldn't save you ♪
♪ That bitter knowledge makes me cry ♪
♪ That's why, you jet black horse ♪
♪ I will never forget you ♪
- [laughs]
- [sighs]
[in English] I'll tell you something
that might make you happy,
but it might also upset you.
Oh! Then go ahead and tell me. Shoot.
Unfortunately, there is no chance
you'll be going extinct.
You don't say.
There are many specimens just like you.
- Have you seen one?
- Yes.
Hang on, one second.
[grunts]
This conversation deserves
another good wine.
You're just like one of my best friends.
He's an epicurean.
A lover of good wine,
of paintings, of beauty, and art.
A Chianti from Tuscany
will be the perfect wine,
but it requires clean new glasses.
May I, señor?
- Yes, you may.
- Thank you.
So… tell me,
in what other ways
is this friend of yours like me?
In many ways, he shares
the same unique personal
and infallible vision of the universe.
And in this universe,
he manages everything
for us common mortals.
[laughs]
Are you implying I'm egocentric?
Yes, absolutely, yes.
Narcissistic and self-absorbed.
But he's so passionate.
He's one of these people
with an incredible presence.
With a catalyzing energy
that infuses you with life.
And once they leave the room,
you're left with… an emptiness.
An absence.
So tell me, who is this friend of yours?
This friend of mine is awake right now,
waiting for that little spark
of genius that changes everything.
And will he find it?
Inevitably.
Inevitably?
He's infallible.
[intense music playing]
Come with me.
I've got something to show you.
Excuse me, um…
Uh, where are we going?
We're off to the chapel.
This is the final resting place
for all my ancestors.
Five generations of Hermosos de Medina.
The twins are buried here.
Leopoldo and Armando.
Just four years old.
A tragic loss.
Push downward on the angel.
I beg your pardon?
Take a hold of the hand of the statue
and push it firmly down.
After you, Damián.
And?
Impressive, right?
Uh, well, the choice of decoration
is quite surprising, for a crypt.
In fact, it's a crypt
hiding beneath another crypt.
- Another of my secrets.
- Ah.
This is where I keep my third treasure.
Do you think my security is good enough?
Your third treasure?
The first one was my art gallery.
And you already broke in there.
Yeah.
- [both chuckle]
- Mm.
And the second one… is my dear wife.
Ah.
[chuckles]
And here…
this is… what I like to call
my secure vault.
So, tell me,
would you really leave me with nothing?
Well, that depends,
because the art of larceny
is very unpredictable, huh?
The art?
Turn the other way.
[keypad beeping]
You can turn around now.
Ta-da!
Go ahead.
You don't trust me?
I'm not that sure it's appropriate.
I'm sharing my deepest and darkest secrets
with you,
and now you don't trust me?
Step across the line.
Cross it.
I insist.
Boo.
Look at me.
Did you actually believe
you could make it this far on your own?
[ominous music rises]
[lock clicks]
["Caballo Prieto Azabache"
by Antonio Aguilar playing]